Guide to the Saul Mills Papers WAG.075
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Photographs, Drawings, Artifacts and Ephemera, circa 1911-1980s, undated
  Series IV: Photographs, Drawings, Artifacts and Ephemera (ca. 1911 -1980s) includes images and artifacts from both Mills' personal and professional lives. Artifacts and ephemera include political buttons, membership cards for labor unions (some with dues stamps affixed) and other organizations; drawings consist of pen and ink drawings probably by Mills' wife, and children's crayon drawings. Most photographs are undated. Group Photographs include an event with Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., that may have taken place in 1965; Miscellaneous Photographs include a portrait of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., and of a drawing of a 1946 proposed New York City "War and Peace Memorial."
  - Artifacts and Ephemera (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 1)
  - Drawings (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 2)
  - Group Photographs (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 4)
  - Negatives (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Portraits of Saul Mills (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 6)
  - Snapshots and Formal Family Photographs (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Photograph, 1961 (Box Shared Tamiment OS001, Folder 1)
  - Family and passport photographs, undated (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 14)
  - Agnes Mills art: scratchboards, undated (Box Shared Tamiment A001, Folder 15)
  - Agnes Mills art: original numbered prints and reprints, 1981-1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 005, Folder 6)
  - Saul Mills Certificates (Box Shared Tamiment 028, Folder 7)
  - Panoramic group photo, gathering of Hebrew National Orphan Home alumni, 1961 (Box Shared Tamiment 032)